Hi everyone, Welcome to G1ant tutorial
In this I will tell you how to add python addon in G1ant robot
so for adding firstly go in tool menu > marketplace
and click on G1ant.Addon.Python
I have installed already that's why showing already installed
close
Go in view menu > Addon
you can see here python is already added
Now tick on python addon
Now I will tell you how I can run a python code in G1ant studio
first I am launching python with the help of program
with the help of keyboard this script is printed in the python
Now I am pressing enter
Now write same code in G1ant as I write in python
you should write understanding python as
first I am defining a string in a variable
we use semicolon for changing the line
in python if I want to print then I write S and press enter key
Now I am writing s and pressing Enter
then above written code run in the python interpreter
Now I am running
First with help of keyboard it is printed as written in G1ant
then script is running in python
as script  run in python
answer is printed
now see how to perform addition
nothing do you do as I told earlier
first launch python ,write same script which u want to run
when this is is printed in python interpreter than it is able to understand what I have to do
this is printed in python
it run after pressing enter
first here printed with keyboard
semicolon mean line change
as entered It run and give answered
here I defining list
simple defining  list  variable
again changing line
now using max function for finding maximum element
and printing maximum element
and pressing enter
first it is printed here
and now pressing enter and his answer is printed here
now see tuple
first simple defining tuple
then I am accessing second and last element
python has index 0 1 2
here 1 means Banana
-1 mean end
end means cherry
both printed after pressing enter
I am wrinting in G1ant studio then If want to hive space in string then I have to use triple prime sign
now run it
simple printed
both answer comes after pressing enter
So guys in this way you can run any python script in G1ant studio
Thank you for this video