hi everyone welcome to the G1ant tutorial
I this video I going to tell about all these command which is available in xlsx addon
with the help of xlsx.open command, we can open any xlsx file
and activate first sheet in it
here I am opening this given Xlsx file
i am only assess for read mode
Isf you want to access for both mode then  write raedwrite
createifnotexist, mean Create that file if it is  not available
and result is stored in this veriable
means G1ant robot will automatically generate an Id that stored in this variable
with the help of this id we can switch xlsx window and ude other command
xlsx.countrow, with help of this command we can count no of row in any xlsx file
Now I am opening this file and no of rows of this file is stored in this variable
you can see here no of rows has been printed
again  here i am using new command which is again .close command
firstly I am opening first excel file then I am opening second xlsx file
and now with the help of id I am closing second xlsx file
now come on another command
I am opening xlsx file with help of xlsx.open command
with the help of xlsx.find command we can find the coordinate of any cell where  a specified value is stored
Here I am finding the coordinate of that cell where this value is available
now printing the colums and rows in the dialog box
you can see here
cloumn 1 and rows 12
xslx.switch , with the help of this command we can switch xslx file which is opened
here I am opening First xlsx file  and second xlsx file
now i am switching first xlsx file again
and xlsx.getvalue command , with the help of this command we can find the value of any specified cell
here I am finding the value of row 1 and column 1
result is stored in a variable and printing the result in a dialog box
again I am switching in second xlsx file
and here also finding the value of same cell and printing the result in a dialog box
and xlsx.setvalues command, with the help of this command we can set the value of a specified
then here  i am saving 123 value in a specified cell (25 row and 1 column )
Now I am running
you can see dhawan and Maneesh are at same location and this value has been saved
in a second xlsx file you can see here
see here 123 has been saved
again opening xlsx file
xlsx.setsheet, with the help of this command we can set a specified sheet
in a active xlsx file
noow i am running it
sheet has been set
thank for this tutorial