Hi everyone welcome to G1ant Tutorial
in this video I am going  to tell about all these command
which is available in watsonaddon
then here I am declaring api variable
here is my api key and now I am declaring serveruri veriable
after that inserting this url in this veriable
with the help of watson.classifyimage command, we can classify any image
here I am classifying this image
and here i am giving my api key
and here I am giving this url.
all extracted information is printed in the dialog box
Now i am going to tell you how Can I generete this api key
firstly open IBM Cloud website
first create his account and login in it
after that you can come on this page and
Go on the Catalog Service
As it is opened , there is available lots of command
As watson assistant , watson studio
Because I have to classify image , click on visual recognition
So I am selecting it
and here
and click on create
as I already clicked
you have to click on this create
and you now reached on this page and click on service credential
click on New credential > add
now you reached on this type of interface
and now copy  it
now paste on notepad or otherwise copy this API key
this is your API key
so in this way you can generate your API key and paste here
now I am running it
you can see here all the extracted information is printed  in dialog box
now come on the another comand
now again I am generating api key
so to generate this api key go in the speech  to text key
as  I earlier told here
Go in catalog
and follow same process to go speech to text process
now again I am declaring serveruri variable
and storing this url
with the help of watson speechtotext we can transcript  any audio file
this is my audio file
here I am storing my api key
this is url and printing the result in a dialog box
now i am running
my audio file is very large
so it may take some time
here you see information has been printed in a dialog box
thank you