Hi everyone Welcome to G1ANT Tutorial
In this Tutorial I will tell you
How to create a addon in a G1ant robot
for this go in Visual studio
click on create Project
Here you have to click on G1ant robot Addon
you can download and install G1ANTRobot Adon from G!ANT github by SDK
click on next
This is the name of my project and this is a location
Here is framework we also can change it
you can see default tempelate of G1ant has been opened
We have to reset it to resolve errors
Go in Project
> manage nuget Package
Here we have to reset it or uninstall it
click on uninstall
Go to browse
and search for G1ANT
install G1ant again
you can see
G1ant has been installed
now I am closing it
we can to defing class for adding the commands
For defining class
Go in Add > Class
here we can write the name of class
suppose
Myfirst command
you have to add .cs extension
Firstly
myfirst command has been opened
first we have to define the namespace of G1ANT language
.Language
in this class you have to define his command
which you want to perform
then I show you my entered command
you can see here
I write this command early
first you have to descriptive your command
name of my command is mynewcommand
in tooltip you have to give the description of command - here this is a demo command
here I define a class my_G1ant_command
as a command class
class may be variable and structure
here I am defining abstract scripter as a public class
we donot have to write any command with in this abstract scripter
here I am defining the argument of a command
we define argument as public  class
and define it in command argument class
Here I am descript the argument as I descripte the command
name of argument is user
If argument is required and I write true otherwise write false
in tool trip we give the description what is the use of this argument
type text to display
here I am defing argument as a textstructure
here we have to take it from user and have to set it
in a text structure command
Here I am defining a excute function here again
defining this excute as a void means it didnot return anything
and  defing as a pubic class
here I am taking the argument which I define earlier
We have to the value of text in message box
I have written this command
go in the build
and click on build solution
solution has been build
Go in addon >
and click on open containing folder
and search for .dll
and copy it
and paste in add on under G1ANT robot
I pasted it
Now I am opening my G1ant robot
G1ANT Robot  has been opened here
go in addon
my addon has been added
I also give name addon it
I define my command
as a usre we can give any text
suppose Hello
Now I am running it
you can see
In this way we can create any addon in G1ANT robot
Thank you