Hi Everyone , Welcome to G1ANT Tutorial
In this tutorial I am going to tell about some daily life project
which I can automate with the help of G1ANT Robot
My first project is On/ OFF the night light
and increase the brightness according to the user
first I write this Program
with the help of ui.click , I am clicking
at this Wpath
after that performing all these operations
after that asking for user if he give yes answer
then again I am clicking
again Night light is closing/off
after that if i want to increase brightness, then I am asking to user
if Yes then How many percentage
here I am incerasing
Now I am going to run
okk Yes
close okk yes
20%
Due to recording i am not able to show you
how brightness will  be increased when recording closed It will work
Now my another project is moving file from one source to another destination
the location of my source is this and location of my destination is this
First I am counting this file from source
after that I am going to my source directory
here I am again printing no of files with the help of for lop
I am coping one by one files and moving to a destination
so that in this way all the files which is available in source will reached to a destination
now I am going to run
5 files to be moved
okk
congratulation 1 file has been moved
there are 5 file in my folder
all the files has been reached in my destination
In this project I perform some operation
with the help of selenium addon first I am opening G1ant manual
and open crickbuzz and again opened crickbuzz
and opened amazon. and want to take information of some project
I want to buy a headphone so I daily watch it to see the increased and decreased price
and printing the price at notepad
Now I am going to run
wow
what
you can see notepad has been closed automatically
In this project I have a image
and want to classify this image and want to extract some information
with the help of watson classifier
you have to make account on IBM cloud and have to make api key before writing this command
after that performing this operation
I am classifing my image and printing the information on notepad
Now I am going to run
you can see all the information has been printed enjoy your day
ya Notepad automatically closed
In this project
all the attachment which is available in gmail, Iam going to download
on the desktop
you can see here
there is no attachment on my desktop now
now attachment download automatically
firstly I am providing some information here
Now again i am opening gmail
and extract the information from here
and here I am using for each and going to each index to the list and finding the attachment
If any attachment is availablr
it downloaded
now I am going to run this program
It will take some time'
because lots of message has to read
its taking much time
but it work
see here
now I am going to desktop
I think
no attachment on my gmail, no attachment is printed
If any attachment is available its downloaded
thank you for this video